<xmlui style="">
    
    
    <page id="HomePodSLA">
        <navigationBar title="Terms and Conditions"/>
        <tableView scrollEnabled="false">
            <section>
                <htmlLabelRow>
                    <![CDATA[ 
                    <html dir="ltr">
                        <head>
                            <meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8"/>
                        </head>
                        <body style="background-color: transparent;color: #000000;text-shadow: none;font-family:-apple-system;font-size:15px;margin-left:20px;margin-right:20px;">
						<pre style="font-family:-apple-system;white-space:pre-wrap;font-size:11px;"><!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD HTML 4.01//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/html4/strict.dtd">
						<html>
						<head>
						<meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8">
						<meta http-equiv="Content-Style-Type" content="text/css">
						<title></title>
						<meta name="Generator" content="Cocoa HTML Writer">
						<meta name="CocoaVersion" content="1504.83">
						<style type="text/css">
						p.p1 {margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font-size: 10.0px; font-family: -apple-system, HelveticaNeue, LucidaGrande}
						p.p2 {margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font-size: 10.0px; font-family: -apple-system, HelveticaNeue, LucidaGrande; min-height: 12.0px}
						span.s1 {text-decoration: underline}
						</style>
						</head>
						<body>
						<p class="p1"><b>IMPORTANT: BY USING YOUR HOMEPOD (“HOMEPOD”), YOU ARE AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE FOLLOWING TERMS:</b></p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>A. <span class="Apple-converted-space">    </span>APPLE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT</b></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>B. <span class="Apple-converted-space">    </span>NOTICES FROM APPLE</b></p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>APPLE INC. </b></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>HOMEPOD SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT</b></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>Single Use License</b></p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>PLEASE READ THIS SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT (“LICENSE”) CAREFULLY BEFORE USING YOUR HOMEPOD OR DOWNLOADING THE SOFTWARE UPDATE ACCOMPANYING THIS LICENSE. BY USING YOUR HOMEPOD OR DOWNLOADING A SOFTWARE UPDATE, AS APPLICABLE, YOU ARE AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS LICENSE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS LICENSE, DO NOT USE THE HOMEPOD OR DOWNLOAD THE SOFTWARE UPDATE. </b></p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>IF YOU HAVE RECENTLY PURCHASED A HOMEPOD AND YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THE LICENSE, YOU MAY RETURN THE HOMEPOD WITHIN THE RETURN PERIOD TO THE APPLE STORE OR AUTHORIZED DISTRIBUTOR WHERE YOU OBTAINED IT FOR A REFUND, SUBJECT TO APPLE’S RETURN POLICY FOUND AT </b><a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/sales_policies/"><b>https://www.apple.com/legal/sales_policies/</b></a><b>.</b></p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>1. General.</b> </p>
						<p class="p1">(a) The software (including Boot ROM code, embedded software and third party software), documentation, interfaces, content, fonts and any data that came with your HomePod (“Original HomePod Software”), as may be updated or replaced by feature enhancements, software updates or system restore software provided by Apple (“HomePod Software Updates”), whether in read only memory, on any other media or in any other form (the Original HomePod Software and HomePod Software Updates are collectively referred to as the “HomePod Software”) are licensed, not sold, to you by Apple Inc. (“Apple”) for use only under the terms of this License. Apple and its licensors retain ownership of the HomePod Software itself and reserve all rights not expressly granted to you. You agree that the terms of this License will apply to any Apple-branded app that may be built-in on your HomePod, unless such app is accompanied by a separate license, in which case you agree that the terms of that license will govern your use of that app.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(b) Apple, at its discretion, may make available future HomePod Software Updates. The HomePod Software Updates, if any, may not necessarily include all existing software features or new features that Apple releases for newer or other models of HomePod.  The terms of this License will govern any HomePod Software Updates provided by Apple, unless such HomePod Software Update is accompanied by a separate license, in which case you agree that the terms of that license will govern.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(c) If you use the express setup feature to set up a new HomePod based on your existing HomePod, you acknowledge and agree that these terms will apply to all other HomePods that you choose to associate with the same iCloud account and that are running the same version of HomePod Software as this HomePod. If you choose to allow automatic HomePod Software Updates, your HomePod will periodically check with Apple for updates to the apps on your device and, if one is available, the update will automatically download and install onto your device. You can turn off the automatic HomePod Updates altogether at any time by going to Settings located in the Home App on your supported and paired iOS device (“Paired iOS Device”).</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>2. Permitted License Uses and Restrictions.</b>  </p>
						<p class="p1">(a) Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, you are granted a limited non-exclusive license to use the HomePod Software on a single HomePod. Except as permitted in Section 2(b) below, and unless as provided in a separate agreement between you and Apple, this License does not allow the HomePod Software to exist on more than one HomePod at a time, and you may not distribute or make the HomePod Software available over a network where it could be used by multiple devices at the same time. This License does not grant you any rights to use Apple proprietary interfaces and other intellectual property in the design, development, manufacture, licensing or distribution of third party devices and accessories, or third party software applications, for use with HomePod. Some of those rights are available under separate licenses from Apple.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(b) Subject to the terms and conditions of this License, you are granted a limited non-exclusive license to download HomePod Software Updates that may be made available by Apple for your model of the HomePod to update or restore the software on any such HomePod that you own or control. This License does not allow you to update or restore any HomePod that you do not control or own, and you may not distribute or make the HomePod Software Updates available over a network where they could be used by multiple devices or multiple computers at the same time.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(c) You may not, and you agree not to or enable others to, copy (except as expressly permitted by this License), decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, attempt to derive the source code of, decrypt, modify, or create derivative works of the HomePod Software or any services provided by the HomePod Software or any part thereof (except as and only to the extent any foregoing restriction is prohibited by applicable law or by licensing terms governing use of open-source components that may be included with the HomePod Software).</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(d) The HomePod Software may be used to reproduce materials so long as such use is limited to reproduction of non-copyrighted materials, materials in which you own the copyright, or materials you are authorized or legally permitted to reproduce. Title and intellectual property rights in and to any content displayed by, stored on or accessed through your HomePod belong to the respective content owner. Such content may be protected by copyright or other intellectual property laws and treaties, and may be subject to terms of use of the third party providing such content. Except as otherwise provided herein, this License does not grant you any rights to use such content nor does it guarantee that such content will continue to be available to you. </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(e) You agree to use the HomePod Software and the Services (as defined in Section 5 below) in compliance with all applicable laws, including local laws of the country or region in which you reside or in which you download or use the HomePod Software and Services. Features of the HomePod Software and the Services may not be available in all languages or regions, some features may vary by region, and some may be restricted or unavailable from your service provider.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(f) A Wi-Fi connection, a Paired iOS Device, Apple ID, iCloud and Apple Music accounts may be required for many features of the HomePod Software, Services, and HomePod. Use of the App Store requires a unique user name and password combination, known as an Apple ID. For more information, please consult the User Guide for your HomePod.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(g) You acknowledge that many features and Services of the HomePod Software transmit data over Wi-Fi and could impact charges to your data plan, and that you are responsible for any such charges.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>3. Transfer.</b> You may not rent, lease, lend, sell, redistribute, or sublicense the HomePod Software. You may, however, make a one-time permanent transfer of all of your license rights to the HomePod Software to another party in connection with the transfer of ownership of your HomePod, provided that: (a) the transfer must include your HomePod and all of the HomePod Software, including all its component parts and this License; (b) you do not retain any copies of the HomePod Software, full or partial, including copies stored on a computer or other storage device; and (c) the party receiving the HomePod Software reads and agrees to accept the terms and conditions of this License.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>4. Consent to Use of Data. </b>HomePod Software features may require information from your Paired iOS Device to provide their respective functions. When you turn on or use these features, such as Siri, details will be provided regarding what information is sent to Apple and how the information may be used.  You can learn more by visiting <a href="https://www.apple.com/privacy/">https://www.apple.com/privacy/</a>.<b> </b>At all times your information will be treated in accordance with Apple’s Privacy Policy, which can be viewed at: <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/">https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/</a>.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>5. Services and Third Party Materials.</b>  </p>
						<p class="p1">(a) The HomePod Software may enable access to Apple’s iTunes Store, App Store, iBooks Store, iCloud, Maps and other Apple and third party services and web sites (collectively and individually, “Services”). Such Services may not be available in all languages or in all countries. Use of these Services requires Internet access and use of certain Services may require an Apple ID, may require you to accept additional terms and may be subject to additional fees. By using this software in connection with an Apple ID, or other Apple Service, you agree to the applicable terms of service for that Service, such as the latest Apple Media Services Terms and Conditions for the country in which you access such Services, which you may access and review at <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/itunes/ww/">https://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/itunes/ww/</a> or the iCloud Terms and Conditions at <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/icloud/ww/">https://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/icloud/ww/</a>.  </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(b) <span class="s1">Podcasts and News Content</span>. Your use of Podcasts and News content accessed through your HomePod is limited solely to personal, noncommercial use, does not transfer any ownership interest to you in the content, and specifically excludes, without limitation, any commercial or promotional use rights in such content. Furthermore, you are prohibited from republishing, retransmitting and reproducing any audio accessed through News as a stand-alone file.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(c) <span class="s1">Maps</span>. The maps service and features of the HomePod Software (“Maps”), including map data coverage, may vary by region. When you use any location-based features within Maps, such as traffic and local search, various location-related and usage information may be sent to Apple, including the real-time geographic location of your HomePod, in order to process your request and help improve Maps. Such location and usage data is collected by Apple in a form that does not personally identify you. <b>By using Maps, you agree and consent to Apple’s and its subsidiaries’ and agents’ transmission, collection, maintenance, processing, and use of this information, to provide and improve the Maps features and service, and other Apple products and services.</b>  Apple may also provide such information, in either an aggregated or non personally identifiable form, to its partners and licensees to help improve their map and location-based products and services. You may disable the location-based functionality of Maps by going to the Location Services of your HomePod by visiting the Home App on your Paired iOS Device and turning off the individual location setting for Maps.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(d) You understand that by using any of the Services, you may encounter content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be identified as having explicit language, and that the results of any search or entering of a particular URL may automatically and unintentionally generate links or references to objectionable material. Nevertheless, you agree to use the Services at your sole risk and that Apple, its affiliates, agents, principals, or licensors shall have no liability to you for content that may be found to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable. </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(e) Certain Services may display, include or make available content, data, information, applications or materials from third parties (“Third Party Materials”) or provide links to certain third party web sites. By using the Services, you acknowledge and agree that Apple is not responsible for examining or evaluating the content, accuracy, completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, legality, decency, quality or any other aspect of such Third Party Materials or web sites. Apple, its officers, affiliates and subsidiaries do not warrant or endorse and do not assume and will not have any liability or responsibility to you or any other person for any third-party Services, Third Party Materials or web sites, or for any other materials, products, or services of third parties. Third Party Materials and links to other web sites are provided solely as a convenience to you. </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(f) Neither Apple nor any of its content providers guarantees the availability, accuracy, completeness, reliability, or timeliness of stock information, location data or any other data displayed by any Services.  Financial information displayed by any Services is for general informational purposes only and should not be relied upon as investment advice. Before executing any securities transaction based upon information obtained through the Services, you should consult with a financial or securities professional who is legally qualified to give financial or securities advice in your country or region. Location data provided by any Services, including the Apple Maps service, is provided for basic navigational and planning purposes only and is not intended to be relied upon in situations where precise location information is needed or where erroneous, inaccurate, time-delayed or incomplete location data may lead to death, personal injury, property or environmental damage.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(g) To the extent that you upload any content through the use of the Services, you represent that you own all rights in, or have authorization or are otherwise legally permitted to upload, such content and that such content does not violate any terms of service applicable to the Services. You agree that the Services contain proprietary content, information and material that is owned by Apple, the site owner or their licensors, and is protected by applicable intellectual property and other laws, including but not limited to copyright. You agree that you will not use such proprietary content, information or materials other than for permitted use of the Services or in any manner that is inconsistent with the terms of this License or that infringes any intellectual property rights of a third party or Apple. No portion of the Services may be reproduced in any form or by any means. You agree not to modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute, or create derivative works based on the Services, in any manner, and you shall not exploit the Services in any unauthorized way whatsoever, including but not limited to, using the Services to transmit any computer viruses, worms, trojan horses or other malware, or by trespass or burdening network capacity. You further agree not to use the Services in any manner to harass, abuse, stalk, threaten, defame or otherwise infringe or violate the rights of any other party, and that Apple is not in any way responsible for any such use by you, nor for any harassing, threatening, defamatory, offensive, infringing or illegal messages or transmissions that you may receive as a result of using any of the Services.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">(h) In addition, Services and Third Party Materials that may be accessed, linked to or displayed on the HomePod are not available in all languages or in all countries or regions. Apple makes no representation that such Services and Third Party Materials are appropriate or available for use in any particular location. To the extent you choose to use or access such Services and Third Party Materials, you do so at your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with any applicable laws, including but not limited to applicable local laws and privacy and data collection laws. Apple and its licensors reserve the right to change, suspend, remove, or disable access to any Services at any time without notice. In no event will Apple be liable for the removal of or disabling of access to any such Services. Apple may also impose limits on the use of or access to certain Services, in any case and without notice or liability. </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>6. Termination.</b> This License is effective until terminated. Your rights under this License will terminate automatically or otherwise cease to be effective without notice from Apple if you fail to comply with any term(s) of this License. Upon the termination of this License, you shall cease all use of the HomePod Software.  Sections 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,11 and 12 of this License shall survive any such termination.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>7. Disclaimer of Warranties.</b> </p>
						<p class="p1">7.1 <span class="Apple-converted-space">    </span>If you are a customer who is a consumer (someone who uses the HomePod Software outside of your trade, business or profession), you may have legal rights in your country of residence which would prohibit the following limitations from applying to you, and where prohibited they will not apply to you. To find out more about rights, you should contact a local consumer advice organization.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">7.2 <span class="Apple-converted-space">    </span>YOU EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT, TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, USE OF THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE AND ANY SERVICES PERFORMED BY OR ACCESSED THROUGH THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND THAT THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO SATISFACTORY QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY AND EFFORT IS WITH YOU. </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">7.3 <span class="Apple-converted-space">    </span>TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE AND SERVICES ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE”, WITH ALL FAULTS AND WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, AND APPLE AND APPLE’S LICENSORS (COLLECTIVELY REFERRED TO AS “APPLE” FOR THE PURPOSES OF SECTIONS 7 AND 8) HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH RESPECT TO THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE AND SERVICES, EITHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND/OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, ACCURACY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">7.4 <span class="Apple-converted-space">    </span>APPLE DOES NOT WARRANT AGAINST INTERFERENCE WITH YOUR ENJOYMENT OF THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE AND SERVICES, THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN, OR SERVICES PERFORMED OR PROVIDED BY, THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, THAT THE OPERATION OF THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE AND SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT ANY SERVICE WILL CONTINUE TO BE MADE AVAILABLE, THAT DEFECTS IN THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE OR SERVICES WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE WILL BE COMPATIBLE OR WORK WITH ANY THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE, APPLICATIONS OR THIRD PARTY SERVICES. INSTALLATION OF THIS HOMEPOD SOFTWARE MAY AFFECT THE AVAILABILITY AND USABILITY OF THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE, APPLICATIONS OR THIRD PARTY SERVICES, AS WELL AS APPLE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES. </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">7.5 <span class="Apple-converted-space">    </span>YOU FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE AND SERVICES ARE NOT INTENDED OR SUITABLE FOR USE IN SITUATIONS OR ENVIRONMENTS WHERE THE FAILURE OR TIME DELAYS OF, OR ERRORS OR INACCURACIES IN, THE CONTENT, DATA OR INFORMATION PROVIDED BY THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE OR SERVICES COULD LEAD TO DEATH, PERSONAL INJURY, OR SEVERE PHYSICAL OR ENVIRONMENTAL DAMAGE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE OPERATION OF NUCLEAR FACILITIES, AIRCRAFT NAVIGATION OR COMMUNICATION SYSTEMS, AIR TRAFFIC CONTROL, LIFE SUPPORT OR WEAPONS SYSTEMS. </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">7.6 <span class="Apple-converted-space">    </span>NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY APPLE OR AN APPLE AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY. SHOULD THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE OR SERVICES PROVE DEFECTIVE, YOU ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR LIMITATIONS ON APPLICABLE STATUTORY RIGHTS OF A CONSUMER, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION AND LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>8. Limitation of Liability. </b>TO THE EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL APPLE, ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS OR PRINCIPALS BE LIABLE FOR PERSONAL INJURY, OR ANY INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, CORRUPTION OR LOSS OF DATA, FAILURE TO TRANSMIT OR RECEIVE ANY DATA (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION COURSE INSTRUCTIONS, ASSIGNMENTS AND MATERIALS), BUSINESS INTERRUPTION OR ANY OTHER COMMERCIAL DAMAGES OR LOSSES, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE AND SERVICES OR ANY THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE OR APPLICATIONS IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE HOMEPOD SOFTWARE OR SERVICES, HOWEVER CAUSED, REGARDLESS OF THE THEORY OF LIABILITY (CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE) AND EVEN IF APPLE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR PERSONAL INJURY, OR OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THIS LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. In no event shall Apple’s total liability to you for all damages (other than as may be required by applicable law in cases involving personal injury) exceed the amount of two hundred and fifty dollars (U.S.$250.00). The foregoing limitations will apply even if the above stated remedy fails of its essential purpose.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>9. Export Control. </b>You may not use or otherwise export or re-export the HomePod Software except as authorized by United States law and the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which the HomePod Software was obtained. In particular, but without limitation, the HomePod Software may not be exported or re-exported (a) into any U.S. embargoed countries or (b) to anyone on the U.S. Treasury Department’s list of Specially Designated Nationals or the U.S. Department of Commerce Denied Person’s List or Entity List or any other restricted party lists. By using the HomePod Software, you represent and warrant that you are not located in any such country or on any such list. You also agree that you will not use the HomePod Software for any purposes prohibited by United States law, including, without limitation, the development, design, manufacture or production of missiles, nuclear, chemical or biological weapons.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>10. Government End Users. </b>The HomePod Software and related documentation are “Commercial Items”, as that term is defined at 48 C.F.R. §2.101, consisting of “Commercial Computer Software” and “Commercial Computer Software Documentation”, as such terms are used in 48 C.F.R. §12.212 or 48 C.F.R. §227.7202, as applicable. Consistent with 48 C.F.R. §12.212 or 48 C.F.R. §227.7202-1 through 227.7202-4, as applicable, the Commercial Computer Software and Commercial Computer Software Documentation are being licensed to U.S. Government end users (a) only as Commercial Items and (b) with only those rights as are granted to all other end users pursuant to the terms and conditions herein. Unpublished-rights reserved under the copyright laws of the United States.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>11. Controlling Law and Severability.</b> This License will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California, excluding its conflict of law principles. This License shall not be governed by the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods, the application of which is expressly excluded. If you are a consumer based in the United Kingdom, this License will be governed by the laws of the jurisdiction of your residence.  If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision, or portion thereof, to be unenforceable, the remainder of this License shall continue in full force and effect.  </p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>12. Complete Agreement; Governing Language.</b> This License constitutes the entire agreement between you and Apple relating to the HomePod Software and supersedes all prior or contemporaneous understandings regarding such subject matter. No amendment to or modification of this License will be binding unless in writing and signed by Apple. Any translation of this License is done for local requirements and in the event of a dispute between the English and any non-English versions, the English version of this License shall govern, to the extent not prohibited by local law in your jurisdiction.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1"><b>13. Third Party Acknowledgements. </b>Portions of the HomePod Software may utilize or include third party software and other copyrighted material. Acknowledgements, licensing terms and disclaimers for such material are contained in the electronic documentation for the HomePod Software, and your use of such material is governed by their respective terms.</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">EA1530</p>
						<p class="p1">10/20/2017</p>
						<p class="p2"><br></p>
						<p class="p1">-------------------------</p>
						<p class="p1"><b>NOTICES FROM APPLE</b></p>
						<p class="p1">If Apple needs to contact you about your product or account, you consent to receive the notices by email. You agree that any such notices that we send you electronically will satisfy any legal communication requirements.</p>
						</body>
						</html>
</pre>
                        </body>
                    </html>
                    ]]>
                </htmlLabelRow>
            </section>
        </tableView>
        
    </page>
    
    <page id="Privacy">
        <navigationBar title="Terms and Conditions"/>
        <tableView scrollEnabled="false">
            <section>
                <htmlLabelRow>
                    <![CDATA[ 
                    <html dir="ltr">
                        <head>
                            <meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8"/>
                        </head>
                        <body style="background-color: transparent;color: #000000;text-shadow: none;font-family:-apple-system;font-size:15px;margin-left:20px;margin-right:20px;">
                            <pre style="font-family:-apple-system;white-space:pre-wrap;font-size:11px;">Privacy Policy<br/><br/>The Apple Privacy Policy was updated on September 19, 2017.<br/><br/>Your privacy is important to Apple. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.<br/><br/>Your California Privacy Disclosures Information Regarding Commercial Electronic Messages in Canada<br/><br/>Collection and Use of Personal Information<br/>Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person.<br/><br/>You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Apple or an Apple affiliated company. Apple and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. You are not required to provide the personal information that we have requested, but, if you chose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our products or services or respond to any queries you may have.<br/><br/>Here are some examples of the types of personal information Apple may collect and how we may use it:<br/><br/>What personal information we collect<br/><br/>	•	When you create an Apple ID, apply for commercial credit, purchase a product, download a software update, register for a class at an Apple Retail Store, contact us or participate in an online survey, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, and credit card information.<br/><br/>	•	When you share your content with family and friends using Apple products, send gift certificates and products, or invite others to participate in Apple services or forums, Apple may collect the information you provide about those people such as name, mailing address, email address, and phone number. Apple will use such information to fulfill your requests, provide the relevant product or service, or for anti-fraud purposes.<br/><br/>	•	In certain jurisdictions, we may ask for a government issued ID in limited circumstances including when setting up a wireless account and activating your device, for the purpose of extending commercial credit, managing reservations, or as required by law.<br/><br/>How we use your personal information<br/><br/>	•	The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Apple’s latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by updating your preferences.<br/><br/>	•	We also use personal information to help us create, develop, operate, deliver, and improve our products, services, content and advertising, and for loss prevention and anti-fraud purposes.<br/><br/>	•	We may use your personal information, including date of birth, to verify identity, assist with identification of users, and to determine appropriate services. For example, we may use date of birth to determine the age of Apple ID account holders.<br/><br/>	•	From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with Apple, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.<br/><br/>	•	We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Apple’s products, services, and customer communications.<br/><br/>	•	If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.<br/><br/>Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information<br/>We also collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:<br/><br/>	•	We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, referrer URL, location, and the time zone where an Apple product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.<br/>	•	We may collect information regarding customer activities on our website, iCloud services, our iTunes Store, App Store, MAC App Store, App Store for Apple TV and iBooks Stores and from our other products and services. This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, products, and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non‑personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.<br/><br/>	•	We may collect and store details of how you use our services, including search queries. This information may be used to improve the relevancy of results provided by our services. Except in limited instances to ensure quality of our services over the Internet, such information will not be associated with your IP address.<br/><br/>	•	With your explicit consent, we may collect data about how you use your device and applications in order to help app developers improve their apps.<br/><br/>If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.<br/><br/>Cookies and Other Technologies<br/>Apple’s websites, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non‑personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.<br/><br/><br/>Ads that are delivered by Apple’s advertising platform may appear in Apple News and in the App Store. If you do not wish to receive ads targeted to your interests from Apple's advertising platform, you can chose to enable Limit Ad Tracking, which will opt your Apple ID out of receiving such ads regardless of what device you are using.  If you enable Limit Ad Tracking on your mobile device, third-party apps cannot use the Advertising Identifier, a non-personal device identifier, to serve you targeted ads. You may still see ads in the App Store or News based on context like your search query or the channel you are reading. In third-party apps, you may see ads based on other information.<br/><br/>Apple and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with Apple more convenient and personal. For example, knowing your first name lets us welcome you the next time you visit the Apple Online Store. Knowing your country and language − and if you are an educator, your school − helps us provide a customized and more useful shopping experience. Knowing someone using your computer or device has shopped for a certain product or used a particular service helps us make our advertising and email communications more relevant to your interests. And knowing your contact information, hardware identifiers, and information about your computer or device helps us personalize your operating system, set up your iCloud service, and provide you with better customer service.<br/>If you want to disable cookies and you’re using the Safari web browser, go to Safari preferences and then to the privacy pane to manage your preferences. On your Apple mobile device, go to Settings, then Safari, scroll down to the Privacy &amp; Security section, and tap on “Block Cookies” to manage your preferences. For other browsers, check with your provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note that certain features of the Apple website will not be available once cookies are disabled.<br/><br/>As is true of most internet services, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit websites and applications, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.<br/><br/>We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, to improve our product and services, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Apple may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.<br/><br/>In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Apple website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.<br/><br/>Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.<br/><br/>Disclosure to Third Parties<br/>At times Apple may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with Apple to provide products and services, or that help Apple market to customers. For example, when you purchase and activate your iPhone, you authorize Apple and your carrier to exchange the information you provide during the activation process to carry out service. If you are approved for service, your account will be governed by Apple and your carrier’s respective privacy policies. Personal information will only be shared by Apple to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.<br/><br/>Service Providers<br/>Apple shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever Apple operates.<br/><br/>Others<br/>It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for Apple to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.<br/><br/>We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.<br/><br/>Protection of Personal Information<br/>Apple takes the security of your personal information very seriously. Apple online services such as the Apple Online Store and iTunes Store protect your personal information during transit using encryption such as Transport Layer Security (TLS). When your personal data is stored by Apple, we use computer systems with limited access housed in facilities using physical security measures. iCloud data is stored in encrypted form including when we utilize third-party storage.<br/><br/>When you use some Apple products, services, or applications or post on an Apple forum, chat room, or social networking service, the personal information and content you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to share or submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.<br/>If you or anyone else using Family Sharing logs on to a device that is owned by a third party, any information shared within your Family—including calendar, location, photos, and iTunes purchases—may be downloaded on to that third-party device thereby disclosing any such shared information. [See About Family Sharing for more information.]<br/><br/>Integrity and Retention of Personal Information<br/>Apple makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.<br/><br/>Access to Personal Information<br/>You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account at https://appleid.apple.com/. For other personal information we hold, we will provide you with access for any purpose including to request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if Apple is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made through the regional Privacy Contact Form.<br/><br/>Children &amp; Education<br/>We understand the importance of taking extra precautions to protect the privacy and safety of children using Apple products and services. Children under the age of 13, or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, are not permitted to create their own Apple IDs, unless their parent provided verifiable consent or as part of the child account creation process in Family Sharing or they have obtained a Managed Apple ID account (where available) through their school. For example, a parent must review the Apple ID and Family Sharing Disclosure and agree to the Consent to Apple’s Collection, Use and Disclosure of Your Child’s Information; and the iTunes Store Terms and Conditions, before they can begin the Apple ID account creation process for their child. In addition, schools that participate in Apple School Manager and have reviewed and consented to the Managed Apple IDs for Students Disclosure may create Managed Apple IDs for students. The Managed Apple IDs for Students Disclosure describes how Apple handles student information and supplements Apple’s Privacy Policy. Learn more about Family Sharing, the Managed Apple IDs and Restrictions for children’s accounts.<br/><br/>If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13, or equivalent minimum age depending on jurisdiction, outside the above circumstances we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.<br/>If at any time a parent needs to access, correct, or delete data associated with their Family Sharing account or child’s Apple ID, they may contact us through our Privacy Contact Form.<br/><br/>Or by using the contact information here.<br/><br/>Location-Based Services<br/>To provide location-based services on Apple products, Apple and our partners and licensees may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your Apple computer or device. Where available, location-based services may use GPS, Bluetooth, and your IP Address, along with crowd-sourced Wi-Fi hotspot and cell tower locations, and other technologies to determine your devices’ approximate location. Unless you provide consent, this location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used by Apple and our partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based products and services. For example, your device may share its geographic location with application providers when you opt in to their location services.<br/><br/>Some location-based services offered by Apple, such as the “Find My iPhone” feature, require your personal information for the feature to work.<br/><br/>Third‑Party Sites and Services<br/>Apple websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties − for example, a third‑party iPhone app.<br/> <br/>Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties. <br/><br/>If you purchase a subscription in a third party app or within News, we create a Subscriber ID that is unique to you and the developer or publisher which we use to provide reports to the developer or publisher that include information about the subscription you purchased, and your country of residence. If you cancel all of your subscriptions with a particular developer or publisher, the Subscriber ID will reset after 180 days if you do not resubscribe. This information is provided to developers so that they can understand the performance of their subscriptions.<br/><br/>International Users<br/>All the information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. Personal information, relating to Apple services, regarding individuals who reside in a member state of the European Economic Area and Switzerland is controlled by Apple Distribution International in Ireland, and processed on its behalf by Apple Inc. Apple uses approved Model Contractual Clauses for the international transfer of personal information collected in the European Economic Area and Switzerland. Apple, as a global company, has a number of legal entities in different jurisdictions which are responsible for the personal information which they collect and which is processed on their behalf by Apple Inc.  For example, point of sale information in our Retail entities outside the U.S. is controlled by our individual Retail entities in each country.  Apple, Online Store and iTunes related personal information may also be controlled by legal entities outside the U.S. as reflected in the terms of each service. <br/><br/>Apple abides by the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) Cross Border Privacy Rules System. The APEC CBPR system provides a framework for organizations to ensure protection of personal information transferred among participating APEC economies.  To learn more about the APEC Certification and Dispute Resolution, please click on the TRUSTe seal. <br/><br/><br/><br/>Our Companywide Commitment to Your Privacy<br/>To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to Apple employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.<br/><br/>Privacy Questions<br/>If you have any questions or concerns about Apple’s Privacy Policy or data processing or if you would like to make a complaint about a possible breach of local privacy laws, please contact us. You can always contact us by phone at the relevant Apple Support number for your country.<br/><br/>All such communications are examined and replies issued where appropriate as soon as possible. If you are unsatisfied with the reply received, you may refer your complaint to the relevant regulator in your jurisdiction. If you ask us, we will endeavor to provide you with information about relevant complaint avenues which may be applicable to your circumstances.<br/><br/>Apple may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.<br/><br/>Apple Inc. 1 Infinite Loop, Cupertino, California, USA, 95014<br/></pre>
                        </body>
                    </html>
                    ]]>
                </htmlLabelRow>
            </section>
        </tableView>
        
    </page>
    
    <page id="iOSWarranty">
        <navigationBar title="Terms and Conditions"/>
        <tableView scrollEnabled="false">
            <section>
                <htmlLabelRow>
                    <![CDATA[ 
                    <html dir="ltr">
                        <head>
                            <meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8"/>
                        </head>
                        <body style="background-color: transparent;color: #000000;text-shadow: none;font-family:-apple-system;font-size:15px;margin-left:20px;margin-right:20px;">
                            <pre style="font-family:-apple-system;white-space:pre-wrap;font-size:11px;">IMPORTANT: BY USING YOUR iPHONE, iPAD, iPOD or APPLE TV PRODUCT YOU ARE AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THE APPLE ONE (1) YEAR LIMITED WARRANTY (“WARRANTY”) AS SET OUT BELOW.<br/><br/>DO NOT USE YOUR PRODUCT UNTIL YOU HAVE READ THE TERMS OF THE WARRANTY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THE WARRANTY, DO NOT USE THE PRODUCT AND RETURN IT WITHIN THE RETURN PERIOD STATED IN APPLE’S RETURN POLICY (FOUND AT www.apple.com/legal/sales_policies/) TO THE APPLE OWNED RETAIL STORE OR THE AUTHORIZED DISTRIBUTOR WHERE YOU PURCHASED IT FOR A REFUND.<br/><br/>Apple One (1) Year Limited Warranty <br/><br/>For Apple Branded Product Only<br/><br/>HOW CONSUMER LAW RELATES TO THIS WARRANTY<br/><br/>THIS WARRANTY GIVES YOU SPECIFIC LEGAL RIGHTS, AND YOU MAY HAVE OTHER RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM STATE TO STATE (OR BY COUNTRY OR PROVINCE). OTHER THAN AS PERMITTED BY LAW, APPLE DOES NOT EXCLUDE, LIMIT OR SUSPEND OTHER RIGHTS YOU MAY HAVE, INCLUDING THOSE THAT MAY ARISE FROM THE NONCONFORMITY OF A SALES CONTRACT. FOR A FULL UNDERSTANDING OF YOUR RIGHTS YOU SHOULD CONSULT THE LAWS OF YOUR COUNTRY, PROVINCE OR STATE. <br/><br/>WARRANTY LIMITATIONS SUBJECT TO CONSUMER LAW<br/><br/>TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THIS WARRANTY AND THE REMEDIES SET FORTH ARE EXCLUSIVE AND IN LIEU OF ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, REMEDIES AND CONDITIONS, WHETHER ORAL, WRITTEN, STATUTORY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. APPLE DISCLAIMS ALL STATUTORY AND IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND WARRANTIES AGAINST HIDDEN OR LATENT DEFECTS, TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. IN SO FAR AS SUCH WARRANTIES CANNOT BE DISCLAIMED, APPLE LIMITS THE DURATION AND REMEDIES OF SUCH WARRANTIES TO THE DURATION OF THIS EXPRESS WARRANTY AND, AT APPLE'S OPTION, THE REPAIR OR REPLACEMENT SERVICES DESCRIBED BELOW. SOME STATES (COUNTRIES AND PROVINCES) DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY (OR CONDITION) MAY LAST, SO THE LIMITATION DESCRIBED ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.<br/><br/>WHAT IS COVERED BY THIS WARRANTY?<br/><br/>Apple Inc. of One Infinite Loop, Cupertino, California, U.S.A. 95014 (“Apple”) warrants the Apple-branded iPhone, iPad, iPod or Apple TV hardware product and the Apple-branded accessories contained in the original packaging (“Apple Product”) against defects in materials and workmanship when used normally in accordance with Apple's published guidelines for a period of ONE (1) YEAR from the date of original retail purchase by the end-user purchaser (&quot;Warranty Period&quot;). Apple’s published guidelines include but are not limited to information contained in technical specifications, user manuals and service communications.<br/><br/>WHAT IS NOT COVERED BY THIS WARRANTY?<br/><br/>This Warranty does not apply to any non-Apple branded hardware products or any software, even if packaged or sold with Apple hardware. Manufacturers, suppliers, or publishers, other than Apple, may provide their own warranties to you – please contact them for further information. Software distributed by Apple with or without the Apple brand (including, but not limited to system software) is not covered by this Warranty. Please refer to the licensing agreement accompanying the software for details of your rights with respect to its use. Apple does not warrant that the operation of the Apple Product will be uninterrupted or error-free. Apple is not responsible for damage arising from failure to follow instructions relating to the Apple Product’s use.<br/><br/>This Warranty does not apply: (a) to consumable parts, such as batteries or protective coatings that are designed to diminish over time, unless failure has occurred due to a defect in materials or workmanship; (b) to cosmetic damage, including but not limited to scratches, dents and broken plastic on ports unless failure has occurred due to a defect in materials or workmanship; (c) to damage caused by use with a third party component or product that does not meet the Apple Product’s specifications (Apple Product specifications are available at www.apple.com under the technical specifications for each product and also available in stores); (d) to damage caused by accident, abuse, misuse, fire, liquid contact, earthquake or other external cause; (e) to damage caused by operating the Apple Product outside Apple’s published guidelines; (f) to damage caused by service (including upgrades and expansions) performed by anyone who is not a representative of Apple or an Apple Authorized Service Provider (“AASP”); (g) to an Apple Product that has been modified to alter functionality or capability without the written permission of Apple; (h) to defects caused by normal wear and tear or otherwise due to the normal aging of the Apple Product; (i) if any serial number has been removed or defaced from the Apple Product; or (j) if Apple receives information from relevant public authorities that the product has been stolen or if you are unable to deactivate passcode-enabled or other security measures designed to prevent unauthorized access to the Apple Product, and you cannot prove in any way that you are the authorized user of the product (eg. by presenting proof of purchase).<br/><br/>IMPORTANT RESTRICTION FOR iPHONE, iPAD AND APPLE TV SERVICE.<br/><br/>Apple may restrict warranty service for iPhone, iPad and Apple TV to the country where Apple or its Authorized Distributors originally sold the device.<br/><br/>YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES<br/><br/>YOU SHOULD MAKE PERIODIC BACKUP COPIES OF THE INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THE APPLE PRODUCT STORAGE MEDIA TO PROTECT THE CONTENTS AND AS A PRECAUTION AGAINST POSSIBLE OPERATIONAL FAILURES. <br/><br/>Before receiving warranty service, Apple or its agents may require that you furnish proof of purchase details, respond to questions designed to assist with diagnosing potential issues and follow Apple's procedures for obtaining warranty service. Before submitting your Apple Product for warranty service you should maintain a separate backup copy of the contents of its storage media, remove all personal information that you want to protect and disable all security passwords.<br/><br/>DURING WARRANTY SERVICE THE CONTENTS OF THE STORAGE MEDIA WILL BE DELETED AND REFORMATTED. APPLE AND ITS AGENTS ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY LOSS OF SOFTWARE PROGRAMS, DATA OR OTHER INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THE STORAGE MEDIA OR ANY OTHER PART OF THE APPLE PRODUCT SERVICED.<br/><br/>Following warranty service your Apple Product or a replacement device will be returned to you as your Apple Product was configured when originally purchased, subject to applicable updates. Apple may install system software updates as part of warranty service that will prevent the Apple Product from reverting to an earlier version of the system software. Third party applications installed on the Apple Product may not be compatible or work with the Apple Product as a result of the system software update. You will be responsible for reinstalling all other software programs, data and information. Recovery and reinstallation of other software programs, data and information are not covered under this Warranty.<br/><br/>Important: Do not open the Apple Product. Opening the Apple Product may cause damage that is not covered by this Warranty. Only Apple or an AASP should perform service on this Apple Product.<br/><br/>WHAT WILL APPLE DO IN THE EVENT THE WARRANTY IS BREACHED?<br/><br/>If during the Warranty Period you submit a claim to Apple or an AASP in accordance with this warranty, Apple will, at its option:<br/><br/>(i) repair the Apple Product using new or previously used parts that are equivalent to new in performance and reliability,<br/><br/>(ii) replace the Apple Product with the same model (or with your consent a product that has similar functionality) formed from new and/or previously used parts that are equivalent to new in performance and reliability, or <br/><br/>(iii) exchange the Apple Product for a refund of your purchase price.<br/><br/>Apple may request that you replace certain user-installable parts or Apple Products. A replacement part or Apple Product, including a user-installable part that has been installed in accordance with instructions provided by Apple, assumes the remaining term of the Warranty or ninety (90) days from the date of replacement or repair, whichever provides longer coverage for you. When an Apple Product or part is replaced or a refund provided, any replacement item becomes your property and the replaced or refunded item becomes Apple's property.<br/><br/>HOW TO OBTAIN WARRANTY SERVICE?<br/><br/>Please access and review the online help resources described below before seeking warranty service. If the Apple Product is still not functioning properly after making use of these resources, please contact an Apple representative or, if applicable, an Apple owned retail store (&quot;Apple Retail&quot;) or AASP, using the information provided below. An Apple representative or AASP will help determine whether your Apple Product requires service and, if it does, will inform you how Apple will provide it. When contacting Apple via telephone, other charges may apply depending on your location.<br/><br/>Online information with details on obtaining warranty service is provided below.<br/><br/>WARRANTY SERVICE OPTIONS<br/><br/>Apple will provide warranty service through one or more of the following options:<br/><br/>(i) Carry-in service. You may return your Apple Product to an Apple Retail or AASP location offering carry-in service. Service will be performed at the location, or Apple Retail or an AASP may send your Apple Product to an Apple Repair Service (“ARS”) location to be serviced. Once you are notified that service is complete, you will retrieve the Apple Product from the Apple Retail or AASP location without delay unless Apple notifies you that the Apple Product will be sent directly to your location from the ARS location.<br/><br/>(ii) Mail-in service. If Apple determines that your Apple Product is eligible for mail-in service, Apple will send you prepaid waybills and if applicable, packaging material and instructions on how to properly pack and address your Apple product, so that you may ship your Apple Product to an ARS or AASP location. Instructions may be sent to you via email or in hard copy with the packaging material. Once service is complete, the ARS or AASP location will return the Apple Product to you. Apple will pay for shipping to and from your location if all instructions regarding the method of packaging and shipping the Apple Product are followed.<br/><br/>(iii) Do-it-yourself (DIY) parts service. DIY parts service allows you to service your own Apple Product. If DIY parts service is available in the circumstances, the following process will apply. <br/><br/>(a) Service where Apple requires return of the replaced Apple Product or part. Apple may require a credit card authorization as security for the retail price of the replacement Apple Product or part and applicable shipping costs. If you are unable to provide credit card authorization, DIY parts service may not be available to you and Apple will offer alternative arrangements for service. Apple will ship a replacement Apple Product or part to you with installation instructions, if applicable, and any requirements for the return of the replaced Apple Product or part. If you follow the instructions, Apple will cancel the credit card authorization, so you will not be charged for the Apple Product or part and shipping to and from your location. If you fail to return the replaced Apple Product or part as instructed or return a replaced Apple Product or part that is ineligible for service, Apple will charge your credit card for the authorized amount.<br/><br/>(b) Service where Apple does not require return of the replaced Apple Product or part. Apple will ship you free of charge a replacement Apple Product or part accompanied by instructions on installation, if applicable, and any requirements for the disposal of the replaced Apple Product or part. <br/><br/>(c) Apple is not responsible for any labor costs you incur relating to DIY parts service. Should you require further assistance, contact Apple at the telephone number listed below.<br/><br/>Apple reserves the right to change the method by which Apple may provide warranty service to you, and your Apple Product’s eligibility to receive a particular method of service. Service will be limited to the options available in the country where service is requested. Service options, parts availability and response times may vary according to country. You may be responsible for shipping and handling charges if the Apple Product cannot be serviced in the country it is in. If you seek service in a country that is not the original country of purchase, you will comply with all applicable import and export laws and regulations and be responsible for all custom duties, V.A.T. and other associated taxes and charges. Where international service is available, Apple may repair or replace Apple Products and parts with comparable Apple Product and parts that comply with local standards.<br/><br/>LIMITATION OF LIABILITY<br/><br/>EXCEPT AS PROVIDED IN THIS WARRANTY AND TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, APPLE IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR DIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES RESULTING FROM ANY BREACH OF WARRANTY OR CONDITION, OR UNDER ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF USE; LOSS OF REVENUE; LOSS OF ACTUAL OR ANTICIPATED PROFITS (INCLUDING LOSS OF PROFITS ON CONTRACTS); LOSS OF THE USE OF MONEY; LOSS OF ANTICIPATED SAVINGS; LOSS OF BUSINESS; LOSS OF OPPORTUNITY; LOSS OF GOODWILL; LOSS OF REPUTATION; LOSS OF, DAMAGE TO, COMPROMISE OR CORRUPTION OF DATA; OR ANY INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL LOSS OR DAMAGE HOWSOEVER CAUSED INCLUDING THE REPLACEMENT OF EQUIPMENT AND PROPERTY, ANY COSTS OF RECOVERING, PROGRAMMING, OR REPRODUCING ANY PROGRAM OR DATA STORED IN OR USED WITH THE APPLE PRODUCT OR ANY FAILURE TO MAINTAIN THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF INFORMATION STORED ON THE APPLE PRODUCT.<br/><br/>THE FOREGOING LIMITATION SHALL NOT APPLY TO DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY CLAIMS, OR ANY STATUTORY LIABILITY FOR INTENTIONAL AND GROSS NEGLIGENT ACTS AND/OR OMISSIONS. APPLE DISCLAIMS ANY REPRESENTATION THAT IT WILL BE ABLE TO REPAIR ANY APPLE PRODUCT UNDER THIS WARRANTY OR REPLACE THE APPLE PRODUCT WITHOUT RISK TO OR LOSS OF INFORMATION STORED IN THE APPLE PRODUCT.<br/><br/>SOME STATES (COUNTRIES AND PROVINCES) DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.<br/><br/>GENERAL<br/><br/>No Apple reseller, agent, or employee is authorized to make any modification, extension, or addition to this Warranty. If any term is held to be illegal or unenforceable, the legality or enforceability of the remaining terms shall not be affected or impaired. This Warranty is governed by and construed under the laws of the country in which the Apple Product purchase took place. Apple or its successor in title is the warrantor under this Warranty.<br/><br/>ONLINE INFORMATION<br/><br/>More information of the following is available online:<br/><br/>International Support Information<br/>www.apple.com/support/country<br/><br/>Apple Authorized Service Providers<br/>support.apple.com/kb/HT1434<br/><br/>Apple Retail Store<br/>www.apple.com/retail/storelist/<br/><br/>Apple Support and Service<br/>www.apple.com/support/contact/phone_contacts.html<br/><br/>Apple Complimentary Support<br/>www.apple.com/support/country/index.html?dest=complimentary<br/><br/>© 2016 Apple Inc. All rights reserved. Apple and the Apple logo are trademarks of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries.<br/><br/>071816-iOS-Warranty-Document-US-v1.2</pre>
                        </body>
                    </html>
                    ]]>
                </htmlLabelRow>
            </section>
        </tableView>
        
    </page>
    
    <page>
        <navigationBar title="Terms and Conditions"/>
        <tableView>
            <section>
                <htmlLabelRow>
                    <![CDATA[ 
                    <html>
                        <head>
                            <meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8"/>
                        </head>
                        <body style="-webkit-text-size-adjust: none;background-color: transparent;color: #000000;text-shadow: none;font-family:-apple-system;font-size: 13px;">
                            <div style="font-weight:bold;">IMPORTANT</div>
                            <div>Please read the following terms before using your iOS device. By using your iOS device, you are agreeing to be bound by the iOS Terms and Conditions. If you choose to use iCloud or Game Center, or both, you are agreeing to be bound by the respective iCloud and Game Center Terms and Conditions.</div>
                        </body>
                    </html>
                    ]]>
                </htmlLabelRow>
                
                <htmlLinkRow accessory="disclosure" url="#HomePodSLA">
                    <![CDATA[ 
                    <html>
                        <head>
                            <meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8"/>
                            <script type="text/javascript">function setHighlighted(isHighlighted) { if (isHighlighted) { document.body.style.color="white"; document.body.style.textShadow=""; } else { document.body.style.color="rgba(0,122,255,1.0)"; document.body.style.textShadow="none"; } }</script>
                            <style type="text/css">
                                div:before { content:" A. "; }
                            </style>
                        </head>
                        <body style="-webkit-text-size-adjust: none;background-color: transparent;color: rgba(0,122,255,1.0);text-shadow: none;font-family:-apple-system;font-size: 13px;">
                            <div style="font-weight:bold;line-height:30px;">HomePod Terms and Conditions</div>
                        </body>
                    </html>
                    ]]>
                </htmlLinkRow>
                
                <htmlLinkRow accessory="disclosure" url="#Privacy">
                    <![CDATA[ 
                    <html>
                        <head>
                            <meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8"/>
                            <script type="text/javascript">function setHighlighted(isHighlighted) { if (isHighlighted) { document.body.style.color="white"; document.body.style.textShadow=""; } else { document.body.style.color="rgba(0,122,255,1.0)"; document.body.style.textShadow="none"; } }</script>
                            <style type="text/css">
                                div:before { content:" B. "; }
                            </style>
                        </head>
                        <body style="-webkit-text-size-adjust: none;background-color: transparent;color: rgba(0,122,255,1.0);text-shadow: none;font-family:-apple-system;font-size: 13px;">
                            <div style="font-weight:bold;line-height:30px;">Privacy Policy</div>
                        </body>
                    </html>
                    ]]>
                </htmlLinkRow>
                
                <htmlLinkRow accessory="disclosure" url="#iOSWarranty">
                    <![CDATA[ 
                    <html>
                        <head>
                            <meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8"/>
                            <script type="text/javascript">function setHighlighted(isHighlighted) { if (isHighlighted) { document.body.style.color="white"; document.body.style.textShadow=""; } else { document.body.style.color="rgba(0,122,255,1.0)"; document.body.style.textShadow="none"; } }</script>
                            <style type="text/css">
                                div:before { content:" C. "; }
                            </style>
                        </head>
                        <body style="-webkit-text-size-adjust: none;background-color: transparent;color: rgba(0,122,255,1.0);text-shadow: none;font-family:-apple-system;font-size: 13px;">
                            <div style="font-weight:bold;line-height:30px;">Warranty</div>
                        </body>
                    </html>
                    ]]>
                </htmlLinkRow>
                
                <htmlLabelRow>
                    <![CDATA[ 
                    <html>
                        <head>
                            <meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8"/>
                        </head>
                        <body style="-webkit-text-size-adjust: none;background-color: transparent;color: #000000;text-shadow: none;font-family:-apple-system;font-size: 13px;">
                            <div style="font-weight:bold;word-wrap:break-word;">PLEASE READ THIS SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT (&quot;LICENSE&quot;) CAREFULLY BEFORE USING YOUR iOS DEVICE OR DOWNLOADING THE SOFTWARE UPDATE ACCOMPANYING THIS LICENSE. BY USING YOUR iOS DEVICE OR DOWNLOADING A SOFTWARE UPDATE, AS APPLICABLE, YOU ARE AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS LICENSE.<br/><br/>IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS LICENSE, DO NOT USE THE iOS DEVICE OR DOWNLOAD THE SOFTWARE UPDATE. IF YOU HAVE RECENTLY PURCHASED AN iOS DEVICE AND YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THE LICENSE, YOU MAY RETURN THE iOS DEVICE WITHIN THE RETURN PERIOD TO THE APPLE STORE OR AUTHORIZED DISTRIBUTOR WHERE YOU OBTAINED IT FOR A REFUND, SUBJECT TO APPLE’S RETURN POLICY FOUND AT http://www.apple.com/legal/sales_policies/.</div>
                        </body>
                    </html>
                    ]]>
                </htmlLabelRow>
            </section>
        </tableView>
        
    </page>
    <serverInfo restricted="false" tos-versions="0:0:0:0:0:526001:0:506401:0:0:0:0:0:548501" current-tos-versions="" client-info="PGlQaG9uZTEwLDE+IDxpUGhvbmUgT1M7MTEuMjsxNUM5MD4gPGNvbS5hcHBsZS5BcHBsZUFjY291bnQvMS4wIChjb20uYXBwbGUuU2hhcmluZy8xLjApPg=="/>
</xmlui>
